http://www.pmcplastics.com/privacy-policy/

262-594-5050SpecialtiesNew Product Design/DevelopmentPlastic Injection Molding ConsultingMold Design ServicesPlastic Injection MoldingPlastic OvermoldingInsert MoldingPlastic WeldingPost-Molding OperationsIndustriesAerospace & DefenseMedical Plastic Injection MoldingFilter Injection MoldingElectronicsFood MachineryResourcesAbout PMCPMC BrochureCase StudiesBlogPhotosEngineered ResinsISO CertificationAccepted Files & FormatsCareersSearch JobsBenefitsCultureTrainingContactContact UsRequest a QuoteOur Team
HomePrivacy Policy
Privacy PolicyPlastic Molded Concepts, Inc. respects your privacy and the purpose for which our site visitors provide us information. We do not share, sell, or rent any of the information collected to any third parties and do not intend to do so in the future.Information CollectedIf you request or submit information to us by sending an Email via the “mail to:” function or filling out a “contact” form, we may save your Email address as well as any other information you may provide. This information may be used to contact you in the future by mail, Email, or phone to convey information about our solutions or services that we feel may benefit you. www.pmcplastics.com Web server collects general data pertaining to every Site Visitor, including the IP address, the domain name, the Web page, the length of time spent on the Site, and the pages accessed while visiting the Site. This information is collected to, among other things, aggregate statistical information, facilitate system administration, and improve the content of the Site. Plastic Molded Concepts.com may also retain the content of the communications that are sent to Plastic Molded Concepts.com customer service representatives. This information helps Plastic Molded Concepts.com to improve/respond to Visitors’ inquiries regarding the Site. Your Email and other information you provide will not be sold to any third party.Information Collected by OthersThis notice addresses only the policy of Plastic Molded Concepts, Inc. website and not sites that users access via links from our site. Plastic Molded Concepts, Inc. is not responsible for the information collection policies of other sites, nor for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our website, nor for the information or content contained therein. Often links to other websites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to our visitors. Users are advised to review the privacy policy of other websites.CookiesPlastic Molded Concepts, Inc. website does not use cookies. Updating, Correcting, and Deleting Personal Information If you would like to have your personal information removed from our records, please send an Email with “Remove personal information” in the subject line.Legally Compelled Disclosure of InformationPlastic Molded Concepts, Inc. may disclose information when legally compelled to do so; in other words, when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires it or for the protection of our legal rights.Periodic Policy ChangesPlease note that Plastic Molded Concepts, Inc. reviews its privacy practices from time-to-time (i.e. to track technology and/or legal changes), and that these practices are subject to change. To ensure continuing familiarity with the most current version of our privacy policy, please bookmark and periodically review this page.This policy statement is made in the name of Plastic Molded Concepts, Inc. and is effective as of February 25, 2011. This statement does not create an agreement between Plastic Molded Concepts, Inc. and users, and as such, does not create any legal rights for any party.Contact Us:Plastic Molded Concepts, Inc. P.O. Box 490, Eagle, Wisconsin 53119 Privacy Policy
